Death thumbs a ride.
Deadly Pickup is a thriller film directed by Dean McKendrick.
Breezy isn't your ordinary hitch-hiker: she's sexy, fun...
and a cold-blooded killer.
As deadly as a viper, Breezy murders her victims with a poisonous ring.
As she preys on highway pickups, Breezy moves from town to town, finally settling briefly as a boarder in the
house of a young couple who have no idea what kind of sexual wolf they've just let in the door.
Breezy Johnson / Brenda Johnson, played by Carter Cruise.
Traci, played by Kira Noir.
Deputy Randall, played by Billy Snow.
Brian, played by William F. Bryant.
Sarah, played by Sarah Hunter.
Sheriff Bates, played by Michael Gaglio.
52 Pick-Up is a 1986 American neo-noir crime film directed by John
Frankenheimer and starring Roy Scheider, Ann-Margret, and Vanity.
It is based on Elmore Leonard's 1974 novel 52 Pickup and is the
second adaptation of it after The Ambassador (1984).
The film explores themes of metal detectorist, femme
fatale, serial killer, hitchhiker, lesbian sex.
The tone is lighthearted and intense.